const DATA = {
  // multiple and binary questions
  "בהד-6": {
    "קורס-1": {
      tools: {
        amountOfQuestions: 3,
        questions: [
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: ` שאלה שאלתית בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `איך קוראים לי?`,
            ans1: `שיר`,
            ans2: `נגה`,
            ans3: `תמר`,
            ans4: `אלון`,
            correctAns: `ans3`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בת כמה אני?`,
            ans1: `16`,
            ans2: `19`,
            ans3: `22`,
            ans4: `80`,
            correctAns: `ans2`,
          },
          {
            type: `binary`,
            question: `תלחצו על נכון`,
            correctAns: `true`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `נכון`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans3`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `נכון`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans2`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `נכון`,
            correctAns: `ans4`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `נכון`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans3`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `נכון`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans2`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `נכון`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans2`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `נכון`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans3`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `נכון`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans2`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `נכון`,
            correctAns: `ans4`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `טעות`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `נכון`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans3`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
          {
            type: `multiple`,
            question: `בלה בלה`,
            ans1: `נכון`,
            ans2: `טעות`,
            ans3: `טעות`,
            ans4: `טעות`,
            correctAns: `ans1`,
          },
        ],
      },
    }, 
  },
};

const COURSES = {
  'בה"ד-6': [
      "קורס-בהד-6",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ],    
  'בה"ד-7': [
      "קורס-בהד-7",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ],    
  'בה"ד-10': [
      "קורס-בהד-10",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ],    
  'בה"ד-11': [
      "קורס-1",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ],    
  'בה"ד-13': [
      "קורס-1",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ],    
  'בה"ד-20': [
      "קורס-1",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ],    
  'בה"ד-חינוך': [
      "קורס-1",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ],      
  'מפקדה': [
      "קורס-1",
      "קורס-2",
      "קורס-3",
      "קורס-4"
  ] 
}